Narrator: go
Speaker 1: go by bus
Narrator: 3
Speaker 1: go for a walk
Narrator: 5
Speaker 1: go home
Narrator: 10
Speaker 1: go out
Narrator: 9
Speaker 1: go shopping
Narrator: 2
Speaker 1: go to a restaurant
Narrator: 11
Speaker 1: go to bed
Narrator: 7
Speaker 1: go to church
Narrator: 1
Speaker 1: go to the beach
Narrator: 6
Speaker 1: go back
Narrator: 4
Speaker 1: go on holiday
Narrator: have
Speaker 2: have a car
Narrator: 12
Speaker 2: have long hair
Narrator: 18
Speaker 2: have breakfast
Narrator: 14
Speaker 2: have a drink
Narrator: 13
Speaker 2: have a good time
Narrator: 16
Speaker 2: have a sandwich
Narrator: 17
Speaker 2: have a shower
Narrator: get
Speaker 1: get a newspaper
Narrator: 23
Speaker 1: get a taxi
Narrator: 19
Speaker 1: get an email
Narrator: 21
Speaker 1: get dressed
Narrator: 25
Speaker 1: get home
Narrator: 22
Speaker 1: get to the airport
Narrator: 24
Speaker 1: get up